{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::0..10.SD_OFF1_INC.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543721796102","data":{"timestamp":" 1543721796102"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 71de6cf8-8da4-48a6-8fc6-2507ecece9c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__0..10.SD_OFF1_INC.34"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sifuri"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIFURI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::0..10.SD_OFF1_INC.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543721798233","data":{"timestamp":" 1543721798233"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 71de6cf8-8da4-48a6-8fc6-2507ecece9c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__0..10.SD_OFF1_INC.34"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sifuri"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIFURI"," userResponse":" SIFURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::0..10.SD_OFF1_INC.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543721803914","data":{"timestamp":" 1543721803913"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 71de6cf8-8da4-48a6-8fc6-2507ecece9c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__0..10.SD_OFF1_INC.34"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" moja"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::0..10.SD_OFF1_INC.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543721805730","data":{"timestamp":" 1543721805730"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 71de6cf8-8da4-48a6-8fc6-2507ecece9c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__0..10.SD_OFF1_INC.34"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" moja"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::0..10.SD_OFF1_INC.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543721809542","data":{"timestamp":" 1543721809542"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 71de6cf8-8da4-48a6-8fc6-2507ecece9c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__0..10.SD_OFF1_INC.34"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbili"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBILI"," userResponse":" MBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::0..10.SD_OFF1_INC.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543721811482","data":{"timestamp":" 1543721811481"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 71de6cf8-8da4-48a6-8fc6-2507ecece9c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__0..10.SD_OFF1_INC.34"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbili"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBILI"," userResponse":" MBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::0..10.SD_OFF1_INC.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543721814568","data":{"timestamp":" 1543721814568"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 71de6cf8-8da4-48a6-8fc6-2507ecece9c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__0..10.SD_OFF1_INC.34"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::0..10.SD_OFF1_INC.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543721816350","data":{"timestamp":" 1543721816349"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 71de6cf8-8da4-48a6-8fc6-2507ecece9c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__0..10.SD_OFF1_INC.34"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::0..10.SD_OFF1_INC.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543721822563","data":{"timestamp":" 1543721822562"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 71de6cf8-8da4-48a6-8fc6-2507ecece9c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__0..10.SD_OFF1_INC.34"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nne"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NNE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::0..10.SD_OFF1_INC.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543721824314","data":{"timestamp":" 1543721824313"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 71de6cf8-8da4-48a6-8fc6-2507ecece9c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__0..10.SD_OFF1_INC.34"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nne"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NNE"," userResponse":" NNE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::0..10.SD_OFF1_INC.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543721828089","data":{"timestamp":" 1543721828088"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 71de6cf8-8da4-48a6-8fc6-2507ecece9c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__0..10.SD_OFF1_INC.34"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tano"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::0..10.SD_OFF1_INC.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543721829901","data":{"timestamp":" 1543721829901"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 71de6cf8-8da4-48a6-8fc6-2507ecece9c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__0..10.SD_OFF1_INC.34"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tano"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::0..10.SD_OFF1_INC.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543721834587","data":{"timestamp":" 1543721834587"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 71de6cf8-8da4-48a6-8fc6-2507ecece9c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__0..10.SD_OFF1_INC.34"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sita"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SITA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::0..10.SD_OFF1_INC.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543721836516","data":{"timestamp":" 1543721836516"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 71de6cf8-8da4-48a6-8fc6-2507ecece9c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__0..10.SD_OFF1_INC.34"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sita"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SITA"," userResponse":" SITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::0..10.SD_OFF1_INC.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543721840092","data":{"timestamp":" 1543721840092"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 71de6cf8-8da4-48a6-8fc6-2507ecece9c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__0..10.SD_OFF1_INC.34"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" saba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::0..10.SD_OFF1_INC.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543721841945","data":{"timestamp":" 1543721841944"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 71de6cf8-8da4-48a6-8fc6-2507ecece9c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__0..10.SD_OFF1_INC.34"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" saba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABA"," userResponse":" SABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::0..10.SD_OFF1_INC.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543721844982","data":{"timestamp":" 1543721844982"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 71de6cf8-8da4-48a6-8fc6-2507ecece9c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__0..10.SD_OFF1_INC.34"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nane"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::0..10.SD_OFF1_INC.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543721846838","data":{"timestamp":" 1543721846838"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 71de6cf8-8da4-48a6-8fc6-2507ecece9c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__0..10.SD_OFF1_INC.34"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nane"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANE"," userResponse":" NANE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::0..10.SD_OFF1_INC.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543721850306","data":{"timestamp":" 1543721850305"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 71de6cf8-8da4-48a6-8fc6-2507ecece9c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__0..10.SD_OFF1_INC.34"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tisa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TISA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::0..10.SD_OFF1_INC.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543721852074","data":{"timestamp":" 1543721852074"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 71de6cf8-8da4-48a6-8fc6-2507ecece9c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__0..10.SD_OFF1_INC.34"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tisa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TISA"," userResponse":" TISA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::0..10.SD_OFF1_INC.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543721855050","data":{"timestamp":" 1543721855049"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 71de6cf8-8da4-48a6-8fc6-2507ecece9c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__0..10.SD_OFF1_INC.34"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::0..10.SD_OFF1_INC.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543721856976","data":{"timestamp":" 1543721856976"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 71de6cf8-8da4-48a6-8fc6-2507ecece9c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__0..10.SD_OFF1_INC.34"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMI"," userResponse":" KUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::0..10.SD_OFF1_INC.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543721859039","data":{"timestamp":" 1543721859038"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 71de6cf8-8da4-48a6-8fc6-2507ecece9c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__0..10.SD_OFF1_INC.34"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" kumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543721859277","data":{"timestamp":" 1543721859277"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 71de6cf8-8da4-48a6-8fc6-2507ecece9c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__0..10.SD_OFF1_INC.34"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMI"," userResponse":" KUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:E..E.all.10.rand.say.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543721890246","data":{"timestamp":" 1543721890246"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 1e154a77-00d5-432d-a720-15efe729cde9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_E..E.all.10.rand.say.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_a_e_j"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:E..E.all.10.rand.say.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543721896874","data":{"timestamp":" 1543721896874"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 1e154a77-00d5-432d-a720-15efe729cde9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_E..E.all.10.rand.say.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_n_v_e"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:E..E.all.10.rand.say.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543721903499","data":{"timestamp":" 1543721903499"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 1e154a77-00d5-432d-a720-15efe729cde9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_E..E.all.10.rand.say.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_e_l_s"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:E..E.all.10.rand.say.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543721910076","data":{"timestamp":" 1543721910076"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 1e154a77-00d5-432d-a720-15efe729cde9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_E..E.all.10.rand.say.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_e_l_p"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:E..E.all.10.rand.say.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543721916670","data":{"timestamp":" 1543721916670"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 1e154a77-00d5-432d-a720-15efe729cde9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_E..E.all.10.rand.say.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_y_i_e"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:E..E.all.10.rand.say.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543721924103","data":{"timestamp":" 1543721924103"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 1e154a77-00d5-432d-a720-15efe729cde9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_E..E.all.10.rand.say.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_y_i_e"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:E..E.all.10.rand.say.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543721930753","data":{"timestamp":" 1543721930753"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 1e154a77-00d5-432d-a720-15efe729cde9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_E..E.all.10.rand.say.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_m_t_e"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:E..E.all.10.rand.say.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543721937379","data":{"timestamp":" 1543721937379"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 1e154a77-00d5-432d-a720-15efe729cde9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_E..E.all.10.rand.say.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_j_e_p"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:E..E.all.10.rand.say.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543721944088","data":{"timestamp":" 1543721944088"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 1e154a77-00d5-432d-a720-15efe729cde9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_E..E.all.10.rand.say.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_e_b_a"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:E..E.all.10.rand.say.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543721950754","data":{"timestamp":" 1543721950753"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 1e154a77-00d5-432d-a720-15efe729cde9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_E..E.all.10.rand.say.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_r_e_v"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:E..E.all.10.rand.say.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543721957446","data":{"timestamp":" 1543721957446"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 1e154a77-00d5-432d-a720-15efe729cde9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_E..E.all.10.rand.say.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_i_e_r"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:E..E.all.10.rand.say.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543721970506","data":{"timestamp":" 1543721970506"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 1e154a77-00d5-432d-a720-15efe729cde9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_E..E.all.10.rand.say.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_i_e_r"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722051650","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722051649"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 1e154a77-00d5-432d-a720-15efe729cde9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_E..E.all.10.rand.say.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_i_e_r"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722051748","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722051748"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" d1a89ee4-4d79-4b53-a01f-708615b00e24"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anafikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAFIKIRIA"," userResponse":" ANAFIKIRIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722061270","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722061270"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" d1a89ee4-4d79-4b53-a01f-708615b00e24"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mumbi anafikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.q2q.AV.rise.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722075574","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722075574"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" fc3dbca0-cd63-4f3a-a925-39e3f79006b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.q2q.AV.rise.32"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_1-9-0"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.q2q.AV.rise.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722083134","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722083133"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" fc3dbca0-cd63-4f3a-a925-39e3f79006b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.q2q.AV.rise.32"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_5-6-4"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.q2q.AV.rise.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722092990","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722092990"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" fc3dbca0-cd63-4f3a-a925-39e3f79006b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.q2q.AV.rise.32"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_8-4-0"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.q2q.AV.rise.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722100509","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722100509"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" fc3dbca0-cd63-4f3a-a925-39e3f79006b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.q2q.AV.rise.32"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_2-5-8"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.q2q.AV.rise.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722106764","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722106764"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" fc3dbca0-cd63-4f3a-a925-39e3f79006b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.q2q.AV.rise.32"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_5-2-3"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.q2q.AV.rise.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722113967","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722113967"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" fc3dbca0-cd63-4f3a-a925-39e3f79006b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.q2q.AV.rise.32"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_6-2-8"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.q2q.AV.rise.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722120197","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722120197"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" fc3dbca0-cd63-4f3a-a925-39e3f79006b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.q2q.AV.rise.32"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_3-9-2"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.q2q.AV.rise.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722127042","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722127042"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" fc3dbca0-cd63-4f3a-a925-39e3f79006b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.q2q.AV.rise.32"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_5-4-9"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.q2q.AV.rise.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722137386","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722137386"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" fc3dbca0-cd63-4f3a-a925-39e3f79006b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.q2q.AV.rise.32"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_9-8-7"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.q2q.AV.rise.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722143711","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722143711"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" fc3dbca0-cd63-4f3a-a925-39e3f79006b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.q2q.AV.rise.32"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_0-6-1"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.q2q.AV.rise.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722150312","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722150312"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" fc3dbca0-cd63-4f3a-a925-39e3f79006b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.q2q.AV.rise.32"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_1_0-6-1"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722160004","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722160004"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 5abade6c-742c-42f1-898c-f2393ec80d6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722162075","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722162075"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 5abade6c-742c-42f1-898c-f2393ec80d6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722164195","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722164194"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 5abade6c-742c-42f1-898c-f2393ec80d6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722167335","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722167335"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 5abade6c-742c-42f1-898c-f2393ec80d6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722169535","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722169535"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 5abade6c-742c-42f1-898c-f2393ec80d6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722171715","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722171714"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 5abade6c-742c-42f1-898c-f2393ec80d6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722174487","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722174487"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 5abade6c-742c-42f1-898c-f2393ec80d6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722176640","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722176640"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 5abade6c-742c-42f1-898c-f2393ec80d6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722178795","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722178794"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 5abade6c-742c-42f1-898c-f2393ec80d6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722181982","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722181982"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 5abade6c-742c-42f1-898c-f2393ec80d6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722184076","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722184076"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 5abade6c-742c-42f1-898c-f2393ec80d6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722186199","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722186199"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 5abade6c-742c-42f1-898c-f2393ec80d6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dada"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722189264","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722189263"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 5abade6c-742c-42f1-898c-f2393ec80d6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722191499","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722191498"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 5abade6c-742c-42f1-898c-f2393ec80d6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722193748","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722193746"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 5abade6c-742c-42f1-898c-f2393ec80d6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Embe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" EMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722196821","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722196820"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 5abade6c-742c-42f1-898c-f2393ec80d6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722199174","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722199174"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 5abade6c-742c-42f1-898c-f2393ec80d6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722201535","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722201534"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 5abade6c-742c-42f1-898c-f2393ec80d6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fagio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAGIO"," userResponse":" FAGIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722204625","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722204624"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 5abade6c-742c-42f1-898c-f2393ec80d6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722206751","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722206750"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 5abade6c-742c-42f1-898c-f2393ec80d6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722208925","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722208924"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 5abade6c-742c-42f1-898c-f2393ec80d6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722212089","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722212089"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 5abade6c-742c-42f1-898c-f2393ec80d6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722214302","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722214302"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 5abade6c-742c-42f1-898c-f2393ec80d6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722216529","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722216529"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 5abade6c-742c-42f1-898c-f2393ec80d6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hunywa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNYWA"," userResponse":" HUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722219737","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722219736"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 5abade6c-742c-42f1-898c-f2393ec80d6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722222191","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722222190"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 5abade6c-742c-42f1-898c-f2393ec80d6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722224581","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722224581"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 5abade6c-742c-42f1-898c-f2393ec80d6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Imara"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMARA"," userResponse":" IMARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722227746","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722227746"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 5abade6c-742c-42f1-898c-f2393ec80d6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722230043","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722230042"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 5abade6c-742c-42f1-898c-f2393ec80d6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722232317","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722232317"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 5abade6c-742c-42f1-898c-f2393ec80d6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" JUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722235371","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722235370"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 5abade6c-742c-42f1-898c-f2393ec80d6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722237613","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722237612"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 5abade6c-742c-42f1-898c-f2393ec80d6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722239858","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722239857"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 5abade6c-742c-42f1-898c-f2393ec80d6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKU"," userResponse":" KUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722242883","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722242883"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 5abade6c-742c-42f1-898c-f2393ec80d6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" L"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722245265","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722245265"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 5abade6c-742c-42f1-898c-f2393ec80d6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722247660","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722247660"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 5abade6c-742c-42f1-898c-f2393ec80d6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722250834","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722250833"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 5abade6c-742c-42f1-898c-f2393ec80d6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722253230","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722253228"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 5abade6c-742c-42f1-898c-f2393ec80d6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" m"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722255651","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722255651"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 5abade6c-742c-42f1-898c-f2393ec80d6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722258616","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722258615"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 5abade6c-742c-42f1-898c-f2393ec80d6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722260890","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722260890"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 5abade6c-742c-42f1-898c-f2393ec80d6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722263182","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722263181"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 5abade6c-742c-42f1-898c-f2393ec80d6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndizi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIZI"," userResponse":" NDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722266471","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722266471"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 5abade6c-742c-42f1-898c-f2393ec80d6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722268719","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722268719"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 5abade6c-742c-42f1-898c-f2393ec80d6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722270937","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722270936"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 5abade6c-742c-42f1-898c-f2393ec80d6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ogelea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OGELEA"," userResponse":" OGELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722274293","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722274291"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 5abade6c-742c-42f1-898c-f2393ec80d6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722276677","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722276677"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 5abade6c-742c-42f1-898c-f2393ec80d6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722279090","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722279090"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 5abade6c-742c-42f1-898c-f2393ec80d6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722282001","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722282001"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 5abade6c-742c-42f1-898c-f2393ec80d6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722284205","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722284205"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 5abade6c-742c-42f1-898c-f2393ec80d6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722286398","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722286397"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 5abade6c-742c-42f1-898c-f2393ec80d6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722289838","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722289838"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 5abade6c-742c-42f1-898c-f2393ec80d6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722292154","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722292154"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 5abade6c-742c-42f1-898c-f2393ec80d6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722294466","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722294466"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 5abade6c-742c-42f1-898c-f2393ec80d6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sikio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKIO"," userResponse":" SIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722297634","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722297634"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 5abade6c-742c-42f1-898c-f2393ec80d6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722299926","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722299925"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 5abade6c-742c-42f1-898c-f2393ec80d6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722302236","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722302235"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 5abade6c-742c-42f1-898c-f2393ec80d6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Taa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAA"," userResponse":" TAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722305318","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722305318"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 5abade6c-742c-42f1-898c-f2393ec80d6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722307494","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722307493"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 5abade6c-742c-42f1-898c-f2393ec80d6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722309652","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722309651"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 5abade6c-742c-42f1-898c-f2393ec80d6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ugali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UGALI"," userResponse":" UGALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722312809","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722312808"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 5abade6c-742c-42f1-898c-f2393ec80d6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722315116","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722315116"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 5abade6c-742c-42f1-898c-f2393ec80d6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722317371","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722317371"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 5abade6c-742c-42f1-898c-f2393ec80d6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Viatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIATU"," userResponse":" VIATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722320627","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722320626"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 5abade6c-742c-42f1-898c-f2393ec80d6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722322834","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722322834"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 5abade6c-742c-42f1-898c-f2393ec80d6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722325113","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722325112"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 5abade6c-742c-42f1-898c-f2393ec80d6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722328396","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722328396"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 5abade6c-742c-42f1-898c-f2393ec80d6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722330747","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722330747"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 5abade6c-742c-42f1-898c-f2393ec80d6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722333090","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722333090"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 5abade6c-742c-42f1-898c-f2393ec80d6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAI"," userResponse":" YAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722336193","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722336193"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 5abade6c-742c-42f1-898c-f2393ec80d6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722338551","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722338551"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 5abade6c-742c-42f1-898c-f2393ec80d6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722340877","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722340877"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 5abade6c-742c-42f1-898c-f2393ec80d6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIPU"," userResponse":" ZIPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722344303","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722344300"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 5abade6c-742c-42f1-898c-f2393ec80d6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722344428","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722344428"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 5abade6c-742c-42f1-898c-f2393ec80d6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIPU"," userResponse":" ZIPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722401148","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722401147"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 5abade6c-742c-42f1-898c-f2393ec80d6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722401205","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722401205"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 75e4a641-2e6b-42d4-8764-be826f945e1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini shingo lako ni refu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" REFU"," userResponse":" REFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722409320","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722409320"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 8678b1f7-b68c-4545-9bd2-83d61775d3fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_f-z-g"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722415361","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722415361"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 8678b1f7-b68c-4545-9bd2-83d61775d3fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_k-f-s"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722420994","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722420993"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 8678b1f7-b68c-4545-9bd2-83d61775d3fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_p-s-f"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722428811","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722428810"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 8678b1f7-b68c-4545-9bd2-83d61775d3fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_y-f-k"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722437362","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722437362"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 8678b1f7-b68c-4545-9bd2-83d61775d3fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_l-f-o"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722440853","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722440853"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 8678b1f7-b68c-4545-9bd2-83d61775d3fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_t-u-f"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722447023","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722447023"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 8678b1f7-b68c-4545-9bd2-83d61775d3fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_f-n-b"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722448946","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722448946"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 8678b1f7-b68c-4545-9bd2-83d61775d3fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_f_f-n-b"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543722463286","data":{"timestamp":" 1543722463286"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_063612"," gameId":" 8678b1f7-b68c-4545-9bd2-83d61775d3fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.88"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_f_f-n-b"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}